bored-night.com 2016-11-04

# Bored at Night? | Bored People | Bored 2 Fun

**Bored-night.com** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate  
our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering  
and dissemination practices for this Web site.

**Third Party Advertising**  
We use Google AdSense and other third-party advertising companies to serve  
ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not  
including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your  
visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site  
and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

**Third Party Cookies**  
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may  
place or recognize a unique �cookie� on your browser.

**Personal Information**  
We do not request any personal information or collect any information that  
personally identifies you or allows you to be personally contacted. Since we  
do not collect any personal information on this Web site, we do not share any  
personal information with any third parties nor do we use any personal  
information for any purposes.

**External Links**  
This site contains links to other sites. **Bored-night.com** is not responsible for  
the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

**Contacting the Web Site**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site,  
or your dealings with this Web site, you can **contact us** .
